Guide to the Yale Glee Club Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1877-2010; Accession 2008-A-142
  - Programs, 1880-2010
    - Season 53, 1913 May 7 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Season 61, 1922 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Photocopies only; includes copies of some news clippings.
    - Season 62, 1922-1923 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Photocopies only.
    - Season 65, 1925-1926 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Photocopies only; includes article.
    - Season 66, 1926-1927 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Season 67: First international tour, 1928 (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Includes photocopy of program (no original).
    - Season 69, 1930 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Season 71, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Season 80: South America tour, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Season 87-89, 1947-1950 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Season 89: War Memorial Dedication, 1950 February 22 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Season 90, 1950-1951 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Season 91, 1951-1952 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Season 92, 1952-1953 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Season 93, 1953-1954 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Season 94, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Season 95, 1955-1956 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Season 96, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Includes Police Amusement License for concert on 1 Mar 1957.
    - Season 97, 1957-1958 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Season 98, 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Season 99, 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 2-3)
    - Season 100, 1960-1961 (Box 6, Folder 4-5)
      Includes summer tour in South America.
    - Season 101, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Season 102, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 7-8)
    - Season 103, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Season 104, 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 2-3)
      Includes Round-the-World tour.
    - Season 105, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Season 106, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Season 107, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
    - Season 108, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 1-2)
    - Season 109, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Season 110, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Season 111, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Season 112, 1972-1973 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Season 114: Summer Tour in South America, 1975 May-June (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Season 115, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Season 116, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Season 117, 1977-1978 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Season 118, 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Season 119, 1979-1980 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Season 120, 1980-1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Season 121, 1981-1982 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Season 122, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Season 123, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Season 124, 1984-1985 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Season 125, 1985-1986 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Season 126, 1986-1987 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Season 127, 1987-1988 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Season 128, 1988-1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Season 129, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Season 130, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Season 131, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Season 132, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Season 133, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Season 134, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Season 135, 1995-1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Season 135 Summer Tour, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Season 136, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Season 137, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Season 138, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Season 139, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Season 140, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Season 141, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Season 142, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Season 143, 2003-2004 (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Season 144, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Season 145, 2005-2006 (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Season 146, 2006-2007 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Season 147, 2007-2008 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Season 148, 2008-2009 (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Season 149, 2009-2010 (Box 11, Folder 10-11)
  - Posters and Flyers, 1950-2010
    - Seasons 90, 95, 1950, 1955-1956 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Seasons 100, 102, 104-109, 1961-1970 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Oversize, 1967-1970, circa 1960s (Box 23, Folder 1)
        Includes some unidentified seasons.
    - Seasons 110-112, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Oversize, 1971 November (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Season 114, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 3)
      Includes Summer Tour.
    - Season 118, 1979 May (Box 23, Folder 2)
      Oversize.
    - Seasons 119, 121-124, 1979-1980, 1981-1985 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Oversize, 1983-1985 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Seasons 126-127, 130, 133, 1986-1987, 1991, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Season 135-139, 1995-2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Oversize, 1996-1999 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Seasons 140-144, 2000-2003, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Seasons 145-149, 2005-2010 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Oversize, 2008-2010 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Administrative records, 1928-2009
    - Seasons 67, 71, 78, 1928, 1932, 1939 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      Includes photocopies only of some documents.
    - Seasons 80, 82, 87-89, 1941, 1943, 1947-1950, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      Includes reminiscences of 1949 European tour by Murray Dodge, 2004; photocopies only of some documents.
    - Seasons 90-94, 1950-1955 (Box 13, Folder 3-4)
    - Seasons 95-99, 1955-1960 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
    - Unidentified season, Circa 1950s (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Seasons 100-104, 1960-1965 (Box 13, Folder 8-9)
    - Seasons 100-104: Tour administration, 1960-1965 (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Sample of certificate of appreciation, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Season 105: International Choral Festival, 1964-1965 (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
      Includes 1964 preparatory work for festival in 1965.
    - Seasons 105-109, 1965-1970 (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Seasons 107-109: Tour administration, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Seasons 110-114, 1970-1975 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Season 114: Latin America
      - Tour administration, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 1)
        Materials are restricted until January 1, 2027 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
      - Tour letters, 1975 Summer (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Seasons 115-119, 1975-1980 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Season 119: Tour administration, 1980 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Seasons 120-124, 1980-1985 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Seasons 122, 124: Tour administration, 1983, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Season 125: 125th Reunion, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      Primarily consists of congratulatory correspondence.
    - Seasons 125-129, 1985-1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Seasons 125-127, 129: Tour administration, 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Seasons 125, 130: 125th and 130th anniversary overviews, 1986, 1989-1991 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Seasons 130-134: Regular and tour administration, 1990-1995 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
      Materials are restricted until January 1, 2036 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
    - Seasons 135-139, 1995-2000 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Season 137: 1998 Doshisha Glee Club visit, 1997-1998 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Seasons 135-139: Tour administration, 1996-2000 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
    - Seasons 140-144, 2000-2005 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
      Materials are restricted until January 1, 2045 as established by Yale Corporation regulations.
    - Seasons 140-144: Tour administration, 2000-2005 (Box 17, Folder 3-5)
    - Seasons 145-148, 2005-2009 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Unidentified seasons, Circa 1940s-1960s (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Calendars, 1980-1999
    Documents Yale Glee Club, and other musical organizations, tours, concerts, meetings, and events.
    - Seasons 120, 122-124, 1980-1985 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Seasons 127-129, 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Seasons 130-134, 1990-1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Seasons 135-138, 1995-1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Press, 1887-2009
    - Season 16, 1887 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Season 67: Summer Tour, 1928 Summer (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Season 76, 1937 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Seasons 80, 85, 88, 1941, 1946, 1949 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Seasons 89-91, 93-94, 1950-1955 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Season 93: Summer Tour, 1954 (Box 19, Folder 4-5)
      - Oversize, 1954 July-August (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Seasons 95-99, 1955-1960 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Oversize, 1957 April (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Unidentified season, Circa 1950s (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Season 100, 1960-1961 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Season 101, 1961-1962 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Season 102, 1962-1963 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Season 103, 1964 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Season 104, 1964-1965 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Seasons 105-106, 1966-1967 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Season 107, 1967-1968 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Season 108, 1968-1969 (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
    - Season 109, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Seasons 110-112, 1970-1973 (Box 20, Folder 6-7)
    - Season 114
      - Barty's birthday, 1975 April (Box 21, Folder 1)
      - Summer Tour, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 1-2)
    - Seasons 115-119, 1975-1980 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Seasons 120-124, 1980-1985 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Seasons 125-129, 1985-1990 (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
    - Seasons 130-134, 1990-1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Seasons 135-139, 1995-2000 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Unidentified season, Circa 1990s (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Seasons 140-143, 2001-2003 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Seasons 145-148, 2005-2009 (Box 22, Folder 4)